A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 8, Accession 2018:011 FA1552
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Audio-Visual Material, 1992-2001; 3
  - The Protestant Heritage - Dr. David Read and Mr. Henry R. Luce, undated; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box T1)
  - Tape Conversion - David Reed and Henry R. Luce, undated; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box T1)